{
    "default": {
        "bg": "#000",
        "output": "#FFF",
        "prompt": "#9eecff",
        "feedback": "#9CF",
        "error": "#E85555"
    },
    "brackets": {
        "bg": "#1d1f21",
        "output": "#ddd",
        "prompt": "#c7b967",
        "feedback": "#6c9ef8",
        "error": "#dc322f"
    },
    "bsod": {
        "bg": "#0D00A9",
        "output": "#FFF",
        "prompt": "#98f7ff",
        "feedback": "#AAA",
        "error": "#ff5010"
    },
    "contrast": {
        "bg": "#000",
        "output": "#FFF",
        "prompt": "#f0ff07",
        "feedback": "#00F",
        "error": "#F00"
    },
    "darkmatter": {
        "bg": "#14191f",
        "output": "#aec2e0",
        "prompt": "#6ee2ff",
        "feedback": "#4cbbff",
        "error": "#a20081"
    },
    "dracula": {
        "bg": "#282A36",
        "output": "#FAFEFF",
        "prompt": "#9eecff",
        "feedback": "#78FF9A",
        "error": "#FBA7E9"
    },
    "energy": {
        "bg": "#000",
        "output": "#4b7c9b",
        "prompt": "#FFF",
        "feedback": "#84fcff",
        "error": "#ff8ef0"
    },
    "funky": {
        "bg": "#4B3974",
        "output": "#01F740",
        "prompt": "#FFF",
        "feedback": "#9CF",
        "error": "#E85555"
    },
    "legalpad": {
        "bg": "#EDE990",
        "output": "#165284",
        "prompt": "#5c5c5c",
        "feedback": "#191919",
        "error": "#c7475f"
    },
    "lightsoda": {
        "bg": "#c9c9c9",
        "output": "#302d8b",
        "prompt": "#5864ff",
        "feedback": "#632b9f",
        "error": "#c40035"
    },
    "music_green": {
        "bg": "#00303e",
        "output": "#f8f8f2",
        "prompt": "#66d9ef",
        "feedback": "#a6e22e",
        "error": "#ec007c"
    },
    "music_yellow": {
        "bg": "#00303e",
        "output": "#f8f8f2",
        "prompt": "#66d9ef",
        "feedback": "#efe158",
        "error": "#ec007c"
    },
    "oldschool": {
        "bg": "#000",
        "output": "#2FFF11",
        "prompt": "#90ff9f",
        "feedback": "#6A6EF4",
        "error": "#940008"
    },
    "orange": {
        "bg": "#000",
        "output": "#FA9918",
        "prompt": "#d06000",
        "feedback": "#8ECEEA",
        "error": "#F3B99F"
    },
    "paper": {
        "bg": "#EEE",
        "output": "#444",
        "prompt": "#165284",
        "feedback": "#00A3CC",
        "error": "#EA006E"
    },
    "rubyblue": {
        "bg": "#112435",
        "output": "#d6e1ff",
        "prompt": "#aba6ee",
        "feedback": "#82C6E0",
        "error": "#af2018"
    },
    "solarized": {
        "bg": "#072B35",
        "output": "#C8DEE2",
        "prompt": "#FFF",
        "feedback": "#58DD4D",
        "error": "#F86057"
    },
    "tomorrow": {
        "bg": "#1d1f21",
        "output": "#c5c8c6",
        "prompt": "#FFF",
        "feedback": "#81a2be",
        "error": "#cc6666"
    },
    "wildcherry": {
        "bg": "#2b1f32",
        "output": "#e15d97",
        "prompt": "#9b5fe0",
        "feedback": "#35ba66",
        "error": "#fed888"
    }
}
